mystart.space 2018-01-19

# Privacy Policy — MyStart.Space

**Privacy Policy**

Introduction

We want to make your experience on our site is satisfying and safe. We understand that you value your privacy. This privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") governs information that you provide to us and information that we gather from your use of this website, and it tells you how we may collect, use, and share this information.

Our website matches consumers seeking products or services with providers of those products or services. We do this by collecting information about you and in turn we provide you products, services and advertising links products or services that you are seeking. We may derive income when visitors click on links going to advertising partner sites. Please remember that when you click on the links to advertising partner websites, you are leaving this website.

Collection of Personal Information

Each time you request information, sign up for a promotion, send us an email, or otherwise transmit information via the Site, MyStart.Space may obtain and collect personally identifiable information including (but not limited to) your name and email address.

Use of Personal Information

MyStart.Space may always use and share with others your personal information:

To enable us to generally respond to you, or to process, validate and verify requests and/or purchase orders;

To fulfill any of your requests;

To send information to you about additional products or services;

To compile and/or distribute information about our website users and usage patterns;

To provide useful information to our website designers for developing new features and services;

To tailor your experience on our websites, e.g., showing content that we believe may interest you or altering the content based on your personal preferences; and in any way we deem advisable to provide better goods or services to our customers.

MyStart.Space may also use personal information for any marketing and survey purpose on behalf of itself and its affiliates and subsidiaries. MyStart.Space may disclose personal information to third party agents and independent contractors that help us conduct our marketing and survey efforts. Further, MyStart.Space may disclose personal information to other companies in connection with marketing efforts including but not limited to direct marketing, which may have no relationship to MyStart.Space. Finally, if MyStart.Space or any of its assets are acquired by or merged with another entity, member information will be one of the transferred assets.

Additionally, MyStart.Space will use or disclose your personal information under the following circumstances: (1) in response to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims; (2) in the event you violate or breach an agreement with MyStart.Space ; (3) we believe you will harm the property or rights of MyStart.Space or those of MyStart.Space's other customers, (4) we believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of MyStart.Space's terms of use, or as otherwise required by law, or (5) personal information may also be shared with or sold to any successor to, or purchaser of, part or all of the assets of MyStart.Space.

Usage Tracking

Usage Data.

Like most internet companies, we track website usage to improve the services we offer. We collect user traffic patterns throughout our website. This information is collected to help improve website design and usability. In addition, we track click-through information, including IP addresses, to our website from the information we send to our users. This is done to gauge the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns, to mitigate fraudulent use and to improve the security of our site and your interaction with the site.

Cookies.

Cookies" are a feature on your browser software. If enabled, cookies may store small amounts of data on your computer about your visit to any of this Site. Cookies assist us in tracking which of our features appeal the most to you and what content you may have viewed on past visits. When you visit this site again, cookies can enable us to customize our content according to your preferences. We may use cookies to: keep track of the number of return visits to this site; accumulate and report aggregate, statistical information on website usage; deliver specific content to you based on your interests or past viewing history; save your password for ease of access to our Site. You can disable cookies, although the Site may not function properly for you. Your browser preferences can be modified to accept or reject all cookies, or request a notification when a cookie is set.

IP Addresses

We automatically track certain information based upon your behavior on the Site. We may use this information to do internal research on our users' demographics, interests, and behavior to better understand, protect and serve you and our community. This information may include the URL that you just came from (whether this URL is on the Site or not), which URL you next go to (whether this URL is on the Site or not), your computer browser information, and your IP address. Your Internet Protocol ("IP") is a unique Internet "address" which is assigned to you by your Internet Service Provider ("ISP"). For local area network ("LAN"), DSL, or cable modem users, an IP address may be permanently assigned to a particular computer. IP addresses are automatically logged by Web servers, collecting information about a user's traffic patterns. While the IP address does not identify an individual by name, it may, with the cooperation of the ISP, be used to locate and identify an individual using the Web. Your IP address can, however, reveal what geographic area you are connecting from, or which ISP you are using. Finally, other websites you visit have IP addresses, and we may collect the IP addresses of those websites and their pages.

Links and Companies providing Offers

This Privacy Policy applies only to this Site. The Site may contain links that direct you to websites owned and operated by other companies. MyStart.Space. does not control, and assumes no responsibility for, the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third party website(s), which may employ cookies and/or collect personal information. In addition, MyStart.Space. will not and cannot censor or edit the content of any third party site. Please be sure to read the privacy policy of each third party website that you visit.

Authorized Users

This site is hosted in the USA and is intended only for residents of the United States. Persons under the age of 18 are not eligible to use this Site unsupervised and we ask that minors do not submit any personal information to us. Persons under the age of 18 may only use this Site in conjunction with and under the supervision of their parents or guardians.

MyStart.Space does not knowingly collect contact or personal information from persons under the age of 13. This Site is not intended to solicit information of any kind from children under the age of 13. It is possible that by fraud or deception we may receive information pertaining to children under the age of 13.

Security

We have implemented reasonable security measures in order to protect information collected through this website from loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction. Please note, however, that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure.

Your California Privacy Rights

Beginning on January 1, 2005, California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits those customers that are California residents to request that MyStart.Space not share your personal information with third parties for their direct marketing use.

To make such a request, write us at:

MyStart.Space

C/O Legal Department – Privacy Officer

150 E Colorado Blvd Suite 201 Pasadena CA 91105

mystartspace@gmail.com

Changes To This Privacy Policy

If we change this Privacy Policy, we will notify you by posting the revised privacy policy on the Site. It is your responsibility to periodically revisit the Site. We may also notify you by sending you an email notification to the email address that you provided to us. It is your responsibility to provide us with your current email address. If we revise our Privacy Policy to broaden our use of your personal information, you may contact us at the address below to request that we either refrain from using your personal information or destroy your personal information.

Contacting Us

MyStart.Space owns and operates the www.MyStart.Space web site.

We can be contacted at the address below:

MyStart.Space

150 E Colorado Blvd Suite 201 Pasadena CA 91105

Updated: April 1, 2016
